Guide to the Yale School of Drama Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale School of Drama records of the dean
1948-2001
RU 727
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
43.5
(87 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, printed materials, speeches, committee files, reports, scripts, theses, and budgets documenting the activities of the dean of the Yale School of Drama. Included are records of Deans Robert Brustein, Howard Stein, and Lloyd Richards.
Yale School of Drama
Brustein, Robert Sanford, 1927-
Richards, Lloyd, 1919-2006
Stein, Howard
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 22-A (YRG 22-A), Central records and records of the dean of the Yale School of Drama.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, printed materials, speeches, committee files, reports, scripts, theses, and budgets documenting the activities of the dean of the Yale School of Drama. Included are records of Deans Robert Brustein, Howard Stein, and Lloyd Richards.
Acting -- Study and teaching; College theater; Deans (Education); Drama -- Study and teaching; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale School of Drama; Yale University -- Administration
- Records of the dean, 1948-1983; Accession 1986-A-026
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018
  - Robert Brustein, 1948-1981
    - A Correspondence
      - 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - ABC Program in Playwriting
      - 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Inquiries (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Acting Department, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Acting/Directing Department
      - 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Acting Fellowships, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Acting Job Inquiries, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Advocates for the Arts, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Activities, 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Association of Canada, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Correspondence
      - 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Fund: Financial Statements
      - 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 21 - 22)
    - Alumni: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - American Educational Theatre Association, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - American National Theatre and Academy, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - American Playwrights Theatre, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Annual Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Applications for Employment, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Applications to the Yale Rep, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 30 - 32)
    - Army, Department of, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Art and Architecture, School of, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Arts Council of Greater New Haven, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Associated Councils of the Arts, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Audience Reaction, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Audition Inquiries
      - 1975 (Box 4, Folder 38 - 39)
      - 1976 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Auditions for "Darkroom" and "Tempest", 1973 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Audition Tour, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - B Correspondence
      - 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Black Students Program, 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Black Workshop, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Board of Permanent Officers of Yale College, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Broadway Theatre League of Rhode Island, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Scholarship (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music Residency, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Budget Office, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - C Correspondence
      - 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Cabaret
      - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Calendar, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Campaign for Yale
      - 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      - 1976 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Campus Police
      - 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - "The Case for Yale", 1975 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - CBS Fellows
      - 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Inquiries, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - City Investing Company, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Commencement
      - 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - 1974 (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Committee of 21, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Crews, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Curriculum and Registrar File
      - 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 84)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 85)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 86)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - D Correspondence
      - 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 88)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 89)
      - 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 90)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 91)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Department of English
      - 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 93)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 94)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Development Office, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - D.F.A. (Doctor of Fine Arts), 1955-1968 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - D.F.A. Committee (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - D.F.A. Program
      - 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 99)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Directing Department, Search for a New Head, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Drama Alumni, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Drama Alumni Association, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 103)
      - Executive Committee, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Drama Alumni Fund
      - 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 105)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 106)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 107)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Drama Library
      - 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 109)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - E Correspondence
      - 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 111)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 112)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 113)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 114)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Ensembles: Workshop Productions, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Eugene O'Neill Memorial Scholarship, 1958-1964 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Euripides at Bay", 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - F Correspondence
      - 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 119)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 120)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 121)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 122)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 123)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Faculty Files
      - 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 125)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 126)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Faculty Memoranda
      - 1966 (Box 10, Folder 128)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 129)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 130)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 131)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes
      - 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 133)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 134)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 135)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 136)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 137)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Film Corporation, 1969-1977 (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - Film Program, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - Films of Yale Repertory Productions, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Financial Aid Information
      - 1974 (Box 11, Folder 143)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 144 - 145)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - First American Congress of Theatre (FACT), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Form Letters, 1957-1967 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Foreign Students, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Fourth International Congress on the Enlightenment, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Fulbright Fellowships, 1961-1966 (Box 12, Folder 154)
    - G Correspondence
      - 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 155)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 156)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 157)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 158)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 159)
    - G-M, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 160)
    - Gifts to the Department of Drama
      - 1956-1967 (Box 12, Folder 163)
      - 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 164)
      - A-L, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 165)
      - M-Z, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 166)
      - Miscellaneous, 1962-1969 (Box 13, Folder 167)
    - Grasso for Governor Campaign, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 168)
    - Guest Lecturers, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 169)
    - H Correspondence
      - 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 171)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 172)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 173)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - H-I Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - House Reports
      - 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 176)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 177)
    - I Correspondence
      - 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 178)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 179)
    - Invitations
      - 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 180)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 181)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 182)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 183)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 184)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 185)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 186)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 187)
    - J Correspondence
      - 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 188)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 189)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 190)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 191)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 192)
    - January Work Month
      - 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 193)
      - 1978 (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Job Applications
      - 1967 (Box 15, Folder 195)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 196)
      - 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 197)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 198 - 199)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 200 - 201)
      - Technical Production, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 202)
      - Junior Company, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 203)
      - Design, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 204)
      - Directing, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 205)
      - Teaching, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 206)
      - Technical, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 207)
    - John Drew Theatre: Applications, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 208 - 209)
    - Tony Johnson's History, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 210)
    - K Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 211)
    - K Correspondence
      - 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 212)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 213)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 214)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 215)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 216)
    - L Correspondence
      - 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 217)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 218)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 219)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 220)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 221)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 222)
    - League of Professional Theatre Training Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 223)
    - Lecturers, 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 224)
    - Letters to Students, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 225)
    - Library
      - 1959-1968 (Box 19, Folder 226)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 227)
    - Loans, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 228)
    - Long Wharf Theatre, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 229)
    - Luce Scholarships, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 230)
    - M Correspondence
      - 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 231)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 232)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 233)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 234)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 235)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Major Productions, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Max, Jerome, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 238)
    - Miller, Jonathan (Associate Dean): Correspondence
      - 1979 Oct - Dec (Box 20, Folder 239)
      - 1979 Apr - Sep (Box 20, Folder 240)
      - 1979 Jan - Mar (Box 20, Folder 241)
      - 1978 Aug - Dec (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - N Correspondence
      - 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 243)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 244)
      - 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 245)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 246)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 247)
    - N-O-P Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 248)
    - N-R, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 249)
    - National Academy of Sciences (Doctorate Records Files), 1961-1966 (Box 20, Folder 250)
      - National Endowment for the Arts
      - 1970-1977 (Box 20, Folder 251)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 21, Folder 253)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 21)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - National Humanities Institute, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - NDEA Title IV Fellows, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - New Haven Arts Council, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - The New Republic
      - 1967-1972 (Box 21, Folder 258)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 260)
    - Notices Posted, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 261)
    - O Correspondence
      - 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 262)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 263)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 264)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 265)
    - Office of the Comptroller
      - 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 266)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 267)
    - Office of Education, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 268)
    - Office of the President
      - 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 269)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 270)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 271)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 272)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 273)
    - Office of the Provost
      - 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 274)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 275)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 276)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 277)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 278)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 279)
    - Office of the Secretary
      - 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 280)
      - 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 281)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 282)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 283)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 284)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 285)
    - Office of the Treasurer
      - 1972-1975 (Box 22, Folder 286)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 287)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 288)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 289)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 290)
    - Office of University Development, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 291)
    - Old Positions Offered, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 292)
    - Outside Companies
      - 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 293)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 294)
    - P Correspondence
      - 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 295)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 296)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 297)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 298)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 299)
    - Personnel, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 300)
    - Phone Messages, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 301)
    - Placement
      - 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 302)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 303)
    - Plans for the Expansions of the Drama School, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 304)
    - Playwriting, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 305)
    - Playwriting Committee (Box 23, Folder 306)
    - Playwriting Program, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 307)
    - Playwriting Program, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 308)
    - Positions Offered
      - 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 309)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 310)
    - Possible Acting Candidates, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 311)
    - Press and Publicity, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 312)
    - Press Releases, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 313)
    - Programming Committee, 1959-1969 (Box 24, Folder 314)
    - Programs, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 315)
    - Prometheus Bound, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 316)
    - Q-R Correspondence
      - 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 317)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 318)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 319)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 320)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 321)
    - R Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 322)
    - Reading List Exams, 1971-1975 (Box 24, Folder 323)
    - Recommendations
      - 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 324)
      - 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 325)
      - 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 326)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 327)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 328)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 329)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 330)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 331)
    - Registrar, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 332)
    - Repertory Company, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 333)
    - Report of the Study Committee of Yale College, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 334)
    - Return Letters for Unsolicited Manuscripts, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 335)
    - S Correspondence
      - 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 337)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 338)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 339)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 340)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 341)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 342)
    - Sarah Lawrence College
      - 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 344)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 345)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 346)
    - Scholarship Problems, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 347)
    - Scholarships, 1971-1976 (Box 28, Folder 348)
    - School of Music
      - 1972 (Box 28, Folder 349)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 350)
    - School Productions, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 351)
    - Scriptreader Reports, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 352)
    - Season: See also ADDENDUM
      - 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 353)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 354)
        - The Darkroom (Box 28, Folder 355)
        - The Frogs (Box 28, Folder 356)
        - Geography of a Horse Dreamer (Box 28, Folder 357)
        - Mahagonny (Box 28, Folder 358)
        - Schlemiel the First (Box 28, Folder 359)
        - The Tempest (Box 28, Folder 360)
        - The Tubs (Box 28, Folder 361)
        - Watergate Classics (Box 28, Folder 362)
      - 1974-1975
        - Memos (Box 28, Folder 363)
        - American Patrol (Box 28, Folder 364)
        - The Father (Box 28, Folder 365)
        - Happy End (Box 28, Folder 366)
        - The Idiots Karamazov (Box 28, Folder 367)
        - The Possessed (Box 28, Folder 368)
        - The Shaft of Love (Box 28, Folder 369)
        - Story Theatre: "Victory" (Box 29, Folder 370)
        - Press and Publicity (Box 29, Folder 371)
      - 1975-1976
        - Bingo (Box 29, Folder 372)
        - Don Juan (Box 29, Folder 373)
        - Dynamite Tonite! (Box 29, Folder 374)
        - General Gorgeous (Box 29, Folder 375)
        - General (Box 29, Folder 376)
        - Troilus and Cressida (Box 29, Folder 377)
        - Press and Publicity (Box 29, Folder 379)
      - 1977-1978
        - Ghost Sonata (Box 29, Folder 380)
        - Man is Man (Box 29, Folder 381)
        - The 1940s Radio Hour (Box 29, Folder 382)
        - Reunion (Box 29, Folder 383)
        - Sganarelle: An Evening of Moliere Farces (Box 29, Folder 384)
        - Terra Nova (Box 29, Folder 385)
        - The Wild Duck (Box 29, Folder 386)
        - Wings (Box 29, Folder 387)
        - Reviews (Box 29, Folder 388)
      - 1978-1979
        - As You Like It (Box 29, Folder 389)
        - The Bundle (Box 29, Folder 390)
        - Buried Child (Box 29, Folder 391)
        - Mahagonny (Box 29, Folder 392)
        - Mistaken Identities (Box 29, Folder 393)
        - The Seagull (Box 29, Folder 394)
        - Tales from Vienna Woods (Box 29, Folder 395)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 396)
    - Shows, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 397)
    - Shubert Fellowships, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 398)
    - Soviet Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 400)
    - Speaking Engagements
      - 1968-1972 (Box 30, Folder 401)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 30, Folder 402)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 403)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 404)
    - Special Scripts
      - 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 405)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 406)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 407)
    - Staff Appointments, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 408)
    - Staff Appointment Forms, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 409)
    - Stage Design, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 410)
    - Student Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 411)
    - Students: Academic
      - 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 412)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 413)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 414)
    - Student Correspondence
      - A-F (Box 31, Folder 415)
      - G-L (Box 31, Folder 416)
      - M-Z (Box 31, Folder 417)
    - Students: Miscellaneous
      - 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 418)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 419)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 420)
    - Student Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 421)
    - Study Commission on Governance, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 422)
    - Subscription Campaign/Box Office Statements, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 423)
    - Subscriptions, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 424)
    - Subscriptions/Box Office, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 425)
    - Subscription Sales, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 426)
    - Summer Cabaret, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 427)
    - Summer Newsletter
      - 1968-1974 (Box 32, Folder 428)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 429)
    - Sunday Film Series
      - 1977 (Box 32, Folder 430)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 431)
    - T Correspondence
      - 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 432)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 433)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 434)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 435)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 436)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 437)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 438)
    - TD&P (Technical Design and Production), 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 439)
    - Telephone Expenses, 176-1977 (Box 32, Folder 440)
    - Telephone Statements, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 441)
    - Theatre Administration, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 442)
    - Theatre Communications Group
      - 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 443)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 32, Folder 444)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 445)
      - Newsletter, 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 446)
    - Theater Magazine, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 447)
    - Theater Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 448)
    - Tour, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 449)
    - U-V-W Correspondence
      - 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 451)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 452)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 453)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 454)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 455)
    - U-Z Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 456)
    - United Way, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 457)
    - University Committee on Co-Education, Report, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 458)
    - University Council, 1967-1971 (Box 33, Folder 459)
    - University Council Committee on Drama, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 460)
    - University Policy, 1966-1968 (Box 33, Folder 461)
    - University: Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 462)
    - Unsolicited Manuscripts
      - 1972-1974 (Box 34, Folder 463)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 464)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 465)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 466)
    - Visitors
      - 1967-1971 (Box 34, Folder 467)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 468)
    - Work Study
      - 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 470)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 471)
    - X-Y-Z Correspondence
      - 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 472)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 473)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 474)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 475)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 476)